<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <MsgGetLocked>Restricted : Cannot retrieve goods. Operation failed.</MsgGetLocked>
  <MsgPutLocked>Restricted : Cannot store goods. Operation failed.</MsgPutLocked>
  <MsgVaultLocked>Restricted : Cannot withdraw currency. Operation failed.</MsgVaultLocked>
  <DlgWarehouseLockAccess>You have violated the contract because of an overdue bill. The following permit will be restricted until you clear all the overdue bills :

{0}

{1}


Please clear the overdue bill ASAP to remove all the restrictions. If the bill remains unpaid at the beginning of a second Service Cycle, your access to the warehouse would be locked permanently and you would lost all the contents in it.</DlgWarehouseLockAccess>
  <DlgVaultLockAccess>You have violated the contract because of an overdue bill. The following permit will be restricted until you clear all the overdue bills :

-Withdraw your currencies
-Pay by vault balance in other services
-Delivering the currency in your valut by RimSilo™ Global DropPod Delivery Service

But you can still put money in and clear the overdue bill with the balance.


Please clear the overdue bill ASAP to remove all the restrictions. If the bill remains unpaid at the beginning of a second Service Cycle, your access to the vault would be locked permanently and you would lost all the currency in it.</DlgVaultLockAccess>
  <DlgNoPods>You haven't purchased any pod. There will be no available capacity for this delivery.
If you still try to continue, the delivery would be failed due to 0 available pods at last.

Please purchase at least one droppod with the "Plus" icon near the button.</DlgNoPods>
  <DlgGlobalDropNotice>Some services are restricted, so items in them cannot be delivered.

Please clear the overdue bill ASAP to make these items available in this page.


Rent for a static chamber is paid in advance when contract starts. So you can bring anyone inside back before the expiration of a chamber.</DlgGlobalDropNotice>
  <DlgTitleLockAccess>Reminder : Access Restricted</DlgTitleLockAccess>
  <DlgTitleNoPods>Reminder : Please Purchase Droppods</DlgTitleNoPods>
  <MsgChamberContentBack>A static chamber contract is expired. Passanger will be delivered to your position.</MsgChamberContentBack>
</LanguageData>
