<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!--Notice:Use "RimSilo™ Client Interface" as English text-->
  <RimBankExtDepositFloatMenuEntryLabel>RimSilo™ Client Interface</RimBankExtDepositFloatMenuEntryLabel>
  <MaintainanceFeeDesc>As is mentioned in the contract, a Maintainance Fee shall be charged and will be used to keep the cargo away from deteriorating,e.g. by freezing or sealing.
If the total market value of the goods isn't very high, you'll be free of this charge. Certainly, if the market value is over a specific amount, maintenance fee will be charged according to a stepped set of prices.

Mouse over the scale below to check the maintainance fee for a specific total market value.</MaintainanceFeeDesc>
  <MaintainanceFeeText>Total Market Value : $ {0}            Maintenance Fee : $ {1}

Details : </MaintainanceFeeText>
  <TipSelectColumn>Click to choose which column to display.</TipSelectColumn>
  <LabelMarketValue>Col : Market Value</LabelMarketValue>
  <LabelMass>Col : Weight</LabelMass>
  <LabelDaysLeft>Col : Days Left</LabelDaysLeft>
  <TipTradeableMarketValue>The market value of an item.
This is the basic value and will not be influenced by Social Skill of a negotiator, the kind of a trader or any extra multipliers.</TipTradeableMarketValue>
  <TipTradeableMass>The weight of an item.</TipTradeableMass>
  <TipDaysLeft>Days before the expiration of a chamber.
If expired, the chamber will be delivered to a currently-active map.

This will be listed one by one if more than one animals in chambers are arranged into the same group in the interface.</TipDaysLeft>
  <FormatDaysLeft> {0} day</FormatDaysLeft>
  <FormatMass> {0} kg</FormatMass>
  <FormatVaultCapacity> ${0} (Total value)</FormatVaultCapacity>
  <NoMapDrop>Cannot target another map.</NoMapDrop>
  <NoSettlementDrop>Cannot target another settlement.</NoSettlementDrop>
  <LabelCurrentMax>Total</LabelCurrentMax>
  <LabelCurrentUsage>Used
{0}</LabelCurrentUsage>
  <ReportStrCapacity>Total Capacity : {0}</ReportStrCapacity>
  <ReportStrRent>Total Rent : {0}</ReportStrRent>
  <ReportStrBase>- Starting : {0}</ReportStrBase>
  <ReportStrExtension>- Expansions : {0}</ReportStrExtension>
  <CapacityExpansionDesc>Capacity per Expansion slot : {0}
Rent per Expansion slot : $ {1}
Subscription fee per Expansion slot : $ {2}
</CapacityExpansionDesc>
  <CapacityExpansionDesc2>Total subscription expense : $ {0}</CapacityExpansionDesc2>
  <MsgCannotShrinkCapUsageLowerBound>Total capacity will be smaller than the usage. Please take out some contents first.</MsgCannotShrinkCapUsageLowerBound>
  <MsgBoxConfirmShrinkCapTitle>Reminder : Give Up Extensions!</MsgBoxConfirmShrinkCapTitle>
  <MsgBoxConfirmShrinkCap>If you give up these capacity extensions, you do lower your cost. But subscription fees won't be refunded, so you'll have to pay them for a second time when buying extensions again. If you do need the capacity, maybe that will be better if you leave them for a while instead of giving it up and subscribing it again.

Are you sure to give up the capacity extensions?</MsgBoxConfirmShrinkCap>
</LanguageData>
